BANANI NAG



@ iambananinag@gmail.com

1 9163811107

◆ AC215/B Prafullakanan(E) Kesto pur Kolkata 700101



Customer support, sales, Banking collection, Banking operations

Bills Payable, Invoices.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth : 25/08/1993

Marital Status: Married

LANGUAGES

English

Bengali (Native)

Hindi

OBJECTIVE

Highly Motivated Individual and a diligent operations associate with experience of maintaining seamless business operation as well as customer service and sales operations, being a fast learner capable to cope up with new ambience and work areas.

EXPERIENCE -

ICICI Bank

05/2022 - 08/2022

Deputy Manager -DSMG

Working as a Collection Manager for NPA customers of HL,PL,CV,Auto Loans

HSBC 01/2020 - 04/2022

Special Project

Work related to Corporate action for Singapore.

Maintaining events according to all the dividend received through fund house statements, and custodian announcement and process the payments to the clients. Handling all voluntary and Mandatory events such as merger, liquidations, Acquisition or take overs.

E-Travels 10/2014 - 12/2019

Office Assistant & Sales

EDUCATION

Indian Institute of Management, Kozhikode 2022-2023

HR Management and Analytics

Pursuing

Vidyasagar University 2016

M.Com

42

University of Calcutta 2014

B.Com

43

West Bengal Council of Higher Secondary Education 2011

Higher Secondary/12th

71%